Guide to the Karen Landahl Papers 1940-2004
University of Chicago Library
- Series IX: Restricted
  - Spectograms - W-, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Spectograms - W-, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Spectograms - S- and D-, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Spectograms - p + + contexts, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Spectograms, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Spectograms, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Spectograms, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Spectograms, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Spectograms, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Patient data - Graphs, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Patient data - A-, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Patient data - D-, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Patient data - H-, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Patient data - M-, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Patient data - M-, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Patient data, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - "L- 017-049," 1995 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Patient data and graphs - "J- 050-082," undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Patient data and graphs - "J- 83-116," undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Patient data and graphs - "L- X013-X016, 001-016," undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Test script for alda, alga, arda, arga - K-, J-, T-, and R-, circa 1997 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Patient data - "4 speakers' formant values for graphs," April 16, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Spectograms - "[da] - [ga] for 4 speakers," circa 1997 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Spectograms - J, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Spectograms - J-, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Spectograms - "J-, Master Spects, 5/28," undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Spectograms - "J- appended stops masters," circa 1997 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Spectograms - "J- LPC and FFT," circa 1997 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Spectograms - K, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Spectograms - "K- appended stops - masters," circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Spectograms - "K- LPC and FFT," circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Spectograms - "R- AL and AR appended masters," circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Spectograms - "R- appended stops masters," circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Spectograms - "R- LPC and FFT," undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Spectograms - T, and notes, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Spectograms - "T- appended stops - masters," circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Spectograms - "T- LPC and FFT," undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Patient data - "Certain measurements for entry into composite data file," undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Presentation graphs and overhead projector transparencies, circa 1997 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Spectograms - Stops and liquids, Y-, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Spectograms, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Perceptual test - Instructions and notes, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Testing consent forms, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Photographs and negatives of patient's mouths, 1985-1986 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Patient X-Rays - C-, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Patient X-Rays - Apert #1909, 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient X-Rays - E-, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient X-Rays - E-, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient images - G-, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Patient X-Rays - Crouzon #3493, 1974-1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Patient X-Rays - Apert #1013, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Patient X-Rays - Apert #984, 1975-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Patient X-Rays - Apert #1949, 1973-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Patient X-Rays - Apert #2183, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient X-Rays - R-, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient images - R-, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Patient X-Rays - Crouzon #2023, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Patient X-Rays - Crouzon #2033, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Patient X-Rays and notes - Crouzon #3589, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Photographs of patients - U- and A-, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Teeth molds, undated (Box 50)